import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map> Question = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    'question':
    '''1.In the Film "OMG Oh My God" Kanji Bhai filed a case against Whom for the damage of his shop due to an earthquake?''',
    'A': 'Bharat Mata',
    'B': 'Parlament',
    'C': 'Mumbai City',
    'D': 'Bhagwan',
    'answer': 'D',
    'bgColor': Colors.purpleAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    'question':
    '''2.What is the new name of the Hyderabad franchise that would replace Deccan Charges in IPL6?''',
    'A': 'Sun Chargers',
    'B': 'Nizam jyothi',
    'C': 'Andhra Aces',
    'D': 'Sun risers Hydrabad',
    'answer': 'D',
    'bgColor': Colors.blueAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    'question':
    '''3.In India under which Union Ministry does the 'Rajbhasha vibhg' function?''',
    'A': 'Home Affairs',
    'B': 'HRD',
    'C': 'Culture',
    'D': 'Law & Justice',
    'answer': 'A',
    'bgColor': Colors.red,
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    'question':
    '''4.According to a proverb,what is said to be 'the mother of invention?''',
    'A': 'Society',
    'B': 'Problem',
    'C': 'Science',
    'D': 'Necessity',
    'answer': 'D',
    'bgColor': Colors.amber,
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    'question':
    '''5.Which actress got  married to siddharth Roy Kapur in 2012?''',
    'A': 'Prachi Desai',
    'B': 'Lisa Roy',
    'C': 'Vidhya Balan',
    'D': 'Sushmita sen',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.lightGreenAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    'question':
    '''6.To Whom did Ravindranath Tagore dedicated his book 'visva parichay' written on science?''',
    'A': 'C v raman',
    'B': 'Satyendra nath Bose',
    'C': 'P c Royn',
    'D': 'Jagdish Chandra Bose',
    'answer': 'B',
    'bgColor': Colors.tealAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    'question':
    '''7.What of these is a chemical element present in the periodic table?''',
    'A': 'Eurocium',
    'B': 'Asiacium',
    'C': 'Americium',
    'D': 'Africium',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.pink,
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    'question':
    '''8.To Whom did Ravindranath Tagore dedicated his book 'visva parichay' written on science?''',
    'A': 'C v raman',
    'B': 'Satyendra nath Bose',
    'C': 'P c Royn',
    'D': 'Jagdish Chandra Bose',
    'answer': 'B',
    'bgColor': Colors.deepOrangeAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    'question': '''9.Which of these is not a work of Kalidas?''',
    'A': 'Raghuvamsham',
    'B': 'Kadambari',
    'C': 'Vikramorvasiyam',
    'D': 'Meghadutam',
    'answer': 'B',
    'bgColor': Colors.purpleAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    'question':
    '''10.According To the devi,Bhagavata, from the tears of which god is the rudraksha tree belived to have been created?''',
    'A': 'Vishnu',
    'B': 'Shiva',
    'C': 'Krishna',
    'D': 'Kamadeva',
    'answer': 'B',
    'bgColor': Colors.lightGreenAccent,
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    'question': '''11.Which of these names 'gold-like'?''',
    'A': 'Sonakshi',
    'B': 'Deepika',
    'C': 'Sonam',
    'D': 'Katrina',
    'answer': 'c',
    'bgColor': Colors.purpleAccent,
  },
];
